<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:image="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1"> 
  <url>
    <loc>http://enerjoy.us/index.html</loc> 
	<image:image>
       <image:loc>http://enerjoy.us/public/images/aloe-vera.jpg</image:loc>
       <image:caption>Aloe vera’s use can be traced back 6,000 years to early Egypt, where the plant was depicted on stone carvings. Known as the “plant of immortality”. -  
Office of Dietary Supplements (ODS), National Institutes of Health (NIH) ods.od.nih.gov</image:caption>
    </image:image>
		<image:image>
       <image:loc>http://enerjoy.us/public/images/coffee.jpg</image:loc>
       <image:caption>Coffee drinkers are less likely to die from heart disease, respiratory disease, stroke, injuries and accidents, diabetes, and infections, although the association was not seen for cancer. These results, published in the May 17, 2012, edition of the New England Journal of Medicine, from a large study of older adults were observed after adjustment for the effects of other risk factors on mortality, such as smoking and alcohol consumption. -  
Office of Dietary Supplements (ODS), National Institutes of Health (NIH) ods.od.nih.gov</image:caption>
    </image:image>
		<image:image>
       <image:loc>http://enerjoy.us/public/images/Enerjoy-bottles.jpg</image:loc>
       <image:caption>ENERJOY is our original botanical elixir inspired by the functional foods and herbs brought across the ocean to Hawaii by the original inhabitants, before there was medicine. Today they are well known for their anti-inflammatory and immunity boosting health benefits. The synergy of the ingredients in our proprietary recipe makes you feel like drinking ENERJOY everyday! We recommend 1 or 2 bottles weekly. - James Nutraceuticals LLC www.ENERJOY.us</image:caption>
    </image:image>
		<image:image>
       <image:loc>http://enerjoy.us/public/images/Enerjoy-lg-Logo.png</image:loc>
       <image:caption>ENERJOY is our original botanical elixir inspired by the functional foods and herbs brought across the ocean to Hawaii by the original inhabitants, before there was medicine. Today they are well known for their anti-inflammatory and immunity boosting health benefits. The synergy of the ingredients in our proprietary recipe makes you feel like drinking ENERJOY everyday! We recommend 1 or 2 bottles weekly. - James Nutraceuticals LLC www.ENERJOY.us</image:caption>
    </image:image>
		<image:image>
       <image:loc>http://enerjoy.us/public/images/ginkgo-biloba.jpg</image:loc>
       <image:caption>The ginkgo tree is one of the oldest types of trees in the world. Extracts from ginkgo leaves are used to make tablets, capsules, or teas. Ginkgo leaf extract has a variety of folk or traditional uses for health purposes. -  
Office of Dietary Supplements (ODS), National Institutes of Health (NIH) ods.od.nih.gov</image:caption>
    </image:image>
		<image:image>
       <image:loc>http://enerjoy.us/public/images/green-tea.jpg</image:loc>
       <image:caption>Tea has been used for medicinal purposes in China and Japan for thousands of years.
Current uses of green tea as a beverage or dietary supplement include improving mental alertness, relieving digestive symptoms and headaches, and promoting weight loss. Green tea and its extracts, such as one of its components, EGCG, have been studied for their possible protective effects against heart disease and cancer. -  
Office of Dietary Supplements (ODS), National Institutes of Health (NIH) ods.od.nih.gov</image:caption>
    </image:image>
		<image:image>
       <image:loc>http://enerjoy.us/public/images/honey.jpg</image:loc>
       <image:caption>Honey's medicinal importance has been documented in the world's oldest medical literatures. Since the ancient times, it has been known to possess antimicrobial property as well as wound-healing activity. -  
Office of Dietary Supplements (ODS), National Institutes of Health (NIH) ods.od.nih.gov</image:caption>
    </image:image>
		<image:image>
       <image:loc>http://enerjoy.us/public/images/noni.jpg</image:loc>
       <image:caption>Historically, many parts of the noni plant were used both externally and internally for a variety of health purposes, alone or in combination with other herbs.
Today, the principal part of the noni plant used for health purposes is the ripe fruit, which is used as a dietary supplement for various chronic diseases, including cancer. -  
Office of Dietary Supplements (ODS), National Institutes of Health (NIH) ods.od.nih.gov</image:caption>
    </image:image>
		<image:image>
       <image:loc>http://enerjoy.us/public/images/turmeric.jpg</image:loc>
       <image:caption>Historically, turmeric has been used in Ayurvedic medicine, primarily in South Asia, for many conditions, including breathing problems, rheumatism, serious pain, and fatigue.
Today, turmeric is used as a dietary supplement for inflammation; arthritis; stomach, skin, liver, and gallbladder problems; cancer; and other conditions. -  
Office of Dietary Supplements (ODS), National Institutes of Health (NIH) ods.od.nih.gov</image:caption>
    </image:image>
  </url>
</urlset>